exotissimo.com 2013-06-23

# Exotissimo Travel Privacy Policiy | Exotissimo

**Exotissimo Travel** respects your privacy. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to you, our visitor. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for this site, [www.exotissimo.com](http://www.exotissimo.com/ "Exotissimo Travel Website").

## We will never give any information about you to others

Our site uses forms in which you give us contact information (like your name, address, and email address) so you can book travel services, request information and support. We use your customer information only when it will be important for us to contact you regarding our web site, new Exotissimo Travel services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please see the "Updating Your Information" section below on how to change your communication preferences.

This site also contains links to other sites. Exotissimo Travel is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. For more information on this subject, please see our terms and conditions.

Our site uses cookies to gather information on online traffic. We use this information from our site statistics (for example your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our site and make your browsing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

## Changing your communication preferences

As a customer of Exotissimo Travel, you may alter your customer information or opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time.

You have the following options to change and modify your customer information:

  * You may send an email to [inquire@exotissimo.com](mailto:inquire@exotissimo.com "Contact Exotissimo Travel")

  * You may click on the unsubscribe link featured at the bottom of the emailing we send you

## Sending Emails

We use emails to communicate with you, to send information that you have requested. We also provide email links, as on our contact us page, to allow you to contact us directly. We strive to promptly reply to your messages.

The information you send to us may be stored and used to improve this site and our products, or it may be reviewed and discarded. However, your information will never be shared with third parties.

## Only If We Have To

As stated previously in this policy, we will never give out your information. The only exceptions to this are, when we are required by law, in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, or we must comply with a legal process served on our web site.

## Changes In Our Practices

If we change our information handling practices or other privacy aspects, we will post those changes on this privacy statement, at least 30 days prior to their implementation.

## Surveys

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and country of residence), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [inquire@exotissimo.com](mailto:inquire@exotissimo.com "Contact Exotissimo Travel")

You can also reach us by post mail at:

**Exotissimo Travel Group  
22nd Floor, Smooth Life Tower  
44 North Sathorn Road, Silom  
Bangrak, Bangkok 10500 THAILAND**
